This video was created by a viewer
Udon noodles in...
Oh, okay, okay.
And the address...
2-2-2...
Bicycle...
Okay.
Maybe 2-2-2.
2-2-2 is south of...
This way is good. Let's just go.
Oh, this way.
No?
Oh, no, we're two minutes out. Oh, we're at 1-1. 1-1 is this way.
2-2 this way... 3... I'll take this one...
Biporn.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
That's a little funny. Blah, blah, blah.
Hello? Hello? Excuse me, sir, it's almost time to come in.
I'm sorry, I'm a little lost. It's in the middle of nowhere.
Okay, okay, what's it like to sleep in an apartment?
It's a little purple. Purple? I see.
Okay, well, let's go there. I'm in a hurry.
I'm sorry, I'm in a hurry.
In a voice. That's not it? Purple.
Beep.
Yes.
Oh, it's YOGAITSU.
Udon?
I ordered udon.
Oh?
Is that it? Is there a difference?
Fried rice.
You ordered fried rice, didn't you?You ordered fried rice, right?
Oh, may I ask you to check the contents of this dish, just in case?
Yes, I do.
Oh, it's a little tilted.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm in a bit of a hurry.
Oh, um, yes.
I don't have any chopsticks.
Huh? You don't have chopsticks?
Oh, you don't have chopsticks?
Oh, I'm sorry. I don't have any chopsticks.
Chopsticks. What should I do?
If you don't have them at home, you can use chopsticks.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Ah, money.
Hand eraser.
What was it again?
Oh, money.
Money.
Oh, I'm paying you.
I'm paying.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Here we go.
Oh, I'm sorry, don't worry.
Oh, don't worry, don't worry.
What is this?
It's called Girls' Eats. It's a delivery place.
Do you know where the station is?
The station is that way.
That way? Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Is everything okay? Here.
I'm sorry.
Oh, this.
I'm sorry. It's still hard work.
Are you okay?Are you okay?
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Are you okay?
Oh, shit. Sweetheart.
Excuse me, I'm Dr. Goulds.
Uh, uh, uh, sorry, Dr. Goulds.
Can I have another one?
Can I still have it?
I'm sorry. Thank you.
You want this one?
No, I don't want it.
Thank you very much. I'm sorry.
I'm so glad.
I'd like you to write the kanji for "begin," which means "to start," as in "to begin a game," "to start a game," "to start a game," or "to start a game.
I understand where the word "begin" comes from.
Yes, I don't know.
You know, it's a woman, right?
I want you to write it neatly one more time.
Then, what's next?
Do you feel it? Yes.
Maybe I can write a little nicer.
Do you know what it means? Well, if you look at the side of your mouth, you'll see that it says...
It says "soil". It says "soil".
If you take the bottom bar out of the soil with your mouth, you get a plus. If you put a minus in your mouth, you get a plus.
Really?
Do you have any questions? Uh, like, uh... like, uh... like, uh, hypomathematics?
Math? I'm in Japanese class. Any questions about Japanese?
So, do you have a future body or something like that in your mind? Future body? Future body, well...
I'm looking to the future, so my legs are going to grow in all directions.
That's why you always tell me to pay the teacher.
Blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
Hello?
Excuse me.
I just ordered a sofa for my house.
Oh, a sofa?Oh, a sofa, yes.
I ordered a sofa and some other things.
But I had to assemble it myself.
I'd like a refund.
Refund?
Yes, sir.
I'd like a refund.
Is that okay?
As soon as possible.
You see, this product...
It's supposed to be assembled by the customer.
No, it didn't say that.
If you look at the instruction manual again...
It is written in the instruction manual.
But I haven't done that kind of thing for a long time.
Oh, is that right?
I see.
Then may I ask your name?
You don't know who I am?
Yes.
I'm Minami Hishida.
Ms. Hishida, yes.
Let me check.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry if I'm in a hurry.
I'm sorry, I just checked.
Maybe it's not our house.
No, I'm sure it is.
I'm sure it is.
Then, um...
Pay-on-delivery.
Can I call someone more important? I'm sorry.
Oh, is that you?
I'm afraid you're not much help.
Uh, but this is the only place I can take calls.
Well, could you have the contractor come over to my place and put it together?
And have him put it together for me?Can I have it assembled?
Oh, we don't have a contractor anymore.
I'm sure there are some guys who can do it.
We'd have to hire a different contractor.
You definitely need a strongman.
We don't have a powerful man.
May I have it shipped freight collect for a refund?
Pay-on-delivery.
Yes, cash on delivery is fine.
Then please do it as soon as possible. Today, please.
Thank you very much. - Thank you.
What?
Hmm.
You're so sweet.
Excuse me.